<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Final Project</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

    <string name="disclaimer">
        Basic first aid refers to the initial process of assessing and addressing the needs of
        someone who has been injured or is in physiological distress due to choking, a heart
        attack, allergic reactions, drugs or other medical emergencies.\n\n Basic first aid allows you to
        quickly determine a person\'s physical condition and the correct course of treatment.\n\n You
        should always seek professional medical help as soon as you are able, but following
        correct first aid procedures can be the difference between life and death.\n\n Follow my entire
        tutorial at your own risk or if you have no alternative STILL AT YOUR OWN RISK.
    </string>

    <string name="check_surrounding">
        •	Evaluate the situation. \n\n
        •	Gather as much information as possible. \n\n
        •	try and figure out the cuase of injury. \n\n
        </string>

    <string name="call_help">
        •	Call authorities or emergency services immediately if you believe someone to be seriously injured.\n\n
        •	Do not leave the victim alone.\n
    </string>

    <string name="care_for_person">
        •	stay calm.\n\n
        •	let them know help is on the way.\n\n
        •	positive reinforcement.\n\n
        </string>

    <string name="steps_to_take_if_the_person_is_unconscious">
        •	Determine responsiveness and Check for breathing and a pulse.\n\n
        •	look\n\n
        •	listen\n\n
        •	feel\n\n
        </string>

    <string name="not_to_do">
       •	Do not feed or hydrate an unconscious person. This could cause choking and possible asphyxiation.\n\n
    •	Do not leave the person alone. Unless you absolutely need to signal or call for help, stay with the person at all times.\n\n
    •	Do not prop up an unconscious person\'s head with a pillow.\n\n
    •	Do not slap or splash with water an unconscious person\'s face. These are movie gimmicks.\n\n
    •	Do not waste time posting the incident on any social media\n\n
    •	Do not attempt to take a selfie with the victim.\n\n
    •	Do not record the incident for personal viewing.\n\n
        </string>

    <string name="title_surroundings">Check the surroundings</string>
    <string name="title_help">Call for help</string>
    <string name="title_care">Care for the person</string>
    <string name="title_unconscious">Steps to take if the person is unconsious</string>
    <string name="title_not_to_do">What not to do</string>
    <string name="title_disclaimer">Disclaimer</string>

    <string name="title_activity_fullscreen">Welcome</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">show help</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">In case of Emergency</string>
</resources>
